Office of the Dean of Undergraduate Students Records, 1907-2015: Finding Aid AC136
University Archives
- Series 4: Residential Advisors, 1965-2000; 13 boxes; 2 folders; 2 items
  - Residential Advisors and Assistant Masters, 1978-1980; 2 boxes
    - Rodden, Edward M. '79, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 66, Folder 26)
    - Rosen, Howard '80, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 66, Folder 27)
    - Russell, Margaret M. '79, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 66, Folder 28)
    - Sacchetti, Raymond '80, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 66, Folder 29)
    - Samuels, Robert M. '80, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 66, Folder 30)
    - Sanders, Reginald L. '81, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 66, Folder 31)
    - Schneider, Mark B. GS, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 66, Folder 32)
    - Schwarzschild, Michael Alen '81, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 66, Folder 33)
    - Simon, Marc '80, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 66, Folder 34)
    - Simons, Jonathan '80, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 66, Folder 35)
    - Slaughter, Anne Marie '80, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 66, Folder 36)
    - Starrett, Lucinda '79, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 66, Folder 37)
    - Stempel, Debra '79, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 66, Folder 38)
    - Stone, David '80, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 66, Folder 39)
    - Swire, Peter '80, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 66, Folder 40)
    - Tannenbaum, Fran '80, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 66, Folder 41)
    - Teutonico, Jeanne '79, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 66, Folder 42)
    - Thomas, Robert M. '80, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 66, Folder 43)
    - Vaughan, Patricia C. '81, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 66, Folder 44)
    - Warbasse, Kristin '79, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 66, Folder 45)
    - Washington, Catherine E. '81, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 66, Folder 46)
    - Webster, Oppit '79, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 66, Folder 47)
    - Weisend, Wendy '79, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 66, Folder 48)
    - White, Colleen '81, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 66, Folder 49)
    - Wilson, R. Cliff '80, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 66, Folder 50)
    - Wolling, Sue '80, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 66, Folder 51)
  - Residential Advisors, 1980-1981; 1 box
    - Adler, Mary '82, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 67, Folder 1)
    - Alagappan, Arun '81, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 67, Folder 2)
    - Bailinson, Jim '81, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 67, Folder 3)
    - Balinski, Maria '82, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 67, Folder 4)
    - Banton, Michelle '82, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 67, Folder 5)
    - Baumann, Andrea '80, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 67, Folder 6)
    - Chacon, Rene '82, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 67, Folder 7)
    - Collins, Elsbeth '82, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 67, Folder 8)
    - Colon, Dominique '81, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 67, Folder 9)
    - Crouch, Taylor '81, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 67, Folder 10)
    - Epstein, Eve '81, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 67, Folder 11)
    - Flaherty, Martin '81, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 67, Folder 12)
    - Franklin, Dona '82, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 67, Folder 13)
    - Gewirth, Andy '81, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 67, Folder 14)
    - Glusker, Ann '81, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 67, Folder 15)
    - Gonzales, Bianca '81, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 67, Folder 16)
    - Hardy, Roger '81, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 67, Folder 17)
    - Hay, Bob '81, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 67, Folder 18)
    - Henry, Sarah '82, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 67, Folder 19)
    - Hill, June '81, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 67, Folder 20)
    - Hunter, Bill '82, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 67, Folder 21)
    - Johnson, Dianne '82, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 67, Folder 22)
    - Johnson, Vietta '82, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 67, Folder 23)
    - Kagan, Diana '81, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 67, Folder 24)
    - Knauer, Susan '81, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 67, Folder 25)
    - Leader, David '81, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 67, Folder 26)
    - Lim, Tillie '81, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 67, Folder 27)
    - Maake, Guy '81, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 67, Folder 28)
    - McDermott, Melora '81, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 67, Folder 29)
    - McGeoch, Lyle '81, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 67, Folder 30)
    - Mead, Michelle '82, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 67, Folder 31)
    - Merrifield, Marshall '82, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 67, Folder 32)
    - Miller, Naomi '81, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 67, Folder 33)
    - Mundy, Liza '82, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 67, Folder 34)
    - Munn, Tracy '82, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 67, Folder 35)
    - Myers, Lyle '81, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 67, Folder 36)
    - Perez, Maria '82, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 67, Folder 37)
    - Phethean, Carol '81, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 67, Folder 38)
    - Rappaport, Nancy '82, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 67, Folder 39)
    - Reed, Don '81, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 67, Folder 40)
    - Remnick, David '81, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 67, Folder 41)
    - Rivers, Mike '81, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 67, Folder 42)
    - Ross, Ellen '81, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 67, Folder 43)
    - Simms, Gaby '81, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 67, Folder 44)
    - Smith, Jon '81, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 67, Folder 45)
    - Stell, Sandra '82, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 67, Folder 46)
    - Streichert, Laura '81, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 67, Folder 47)
    - Trask, Becky '81, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 67, Folder 48)
    - Figueroa, Jose '81 (Transfer/Visiting Student Advisor), dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 67, Folder 49)
    - Evaul, Anne '82 (Alternate), dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 67, Folder 50)
  - Residential Advisors, 1981-1982; 1 box
    - Challenner, Daniel '81, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 67, Folder 51)
    - Cooper, Antoinette L. '81, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 67, Folder 52)
    - Gorelick, Richard '82, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 67, Folder 53)
    - Mayer, Carl '81, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 67, Folder 54)
    - McNeal, Franne '82, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 67, Folder 55)
    - Ng, Cindy '82, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 67, Folder 56)
    - Savin, Jody '82, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 67, Folder 57)
    - Tan, Jee-Peng GS, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 67, Folder 58)
    - Silverman, Debra '82, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 67, Folder 59)
    - William, Lael '82, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 67, Folder 60)
    - Moore, Andrew '83, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 67, Folder 61)
    - Moore, William '82, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 67, Folder 62)
    - Odim, Nnena '83, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 67, Folder 63)
    - Ryan, Joseph '83, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 67, Folder 64)
    - Ryan, William E. '83, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 67, Folder 65)
    - Simons, Jefferey '83, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 67, Folder 66)
    - Smith, David S. '82, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 67, Folder 67)
    - Stroman, Jay '82, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 67, Folder 68)
    - Trice, Michael '82, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 67, Folder 69)
    - Vogel, Steve '83, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 67, Folder 70)
    - William, Gayle E. '82, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 67, Folder 71)
    - Windsor, Charles Browning '82, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 67, Folder 72)
    - Winters, Clinton W. '82, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 67, Folder 73)
    - Wong, Cing-Yuen '83, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 67, Folder 74)
    - Wysham, Daphne '83, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 67, Folder 75)
    - Yaure, Christopher '82, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 67, Folder 76)
    - Lempert, Ted '83, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 67, Folder 77)
    - Levan, Nanette '82, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 67, Folder 78)
    - Light, David C. '83, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 67, Folder 79)
    - Malamut, Michael E. '82, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 67, Folder 80)
    - McSpiritt, James '82, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 67, Folder 81)
    - Mednicoff, David '82, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 67, Folder 82)
    - Meistering, Terry '82, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 67, Folder 83)
    - Miller, Howard '82, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 67, Folder 84)
    - Mohrmann, John '83, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 67, Folder 85)
    - Diaz, Arthur Cesare '82, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 67, Folder 86)
    - Dix, Willard M. GS, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 67, Folder 87)
    - Flanagan, Elaine D. '82, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 67, Folder 88)
    - Foster, Andrew '83, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 67, Folder 89)
    - Fradd, Rene Brandon '83, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 67, Folder 90)
    - Franklin, Karen '82, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 67, Folder 91)
    - Fridorich, Dean '82, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 67, Folder 92)
    - Frorer, Peter '83, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 67, Folder 93)
    - Green, Judith '83, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 67, Folder 94)
    - Gurian, John '83, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 67, Folder 95)
    - Hammer, David '82, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 67, Folder 96)
    - Hausman, Madelaine '82, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 67, Folder 97)
    - Hecht, Herbert W. '83, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 67, Folder 98)
    - Kendrick, Ann R. '83, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 67, Folder 99)
    - Allard, Andy '83, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 67, Folder 100)
    - Andrews, Gregory R. '83, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 67, Folder 101)
    - Andrews, John '83, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 67, Folder 102)
    - Aronin, Heidi '82, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 67, Folder 103)
    - Barth, Christopher '82, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 67, Folder 104)
    - Bartholomae, Eric '82, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 67, Folder 105)
    - Berman, Jessica '83, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 67, Folder 106)
    - Borchard, Douglas '82, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 67, Folder 107)
    - Bull, Samuel B. '82, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 67, Folder 108)
    - Candilis, Philip '83, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 67, Folder 109)
    - Cavanaugh, Timothy '83, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 67, Folder 110)
    - Cobau, William G. '83, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 67, Folder 111)
    - Coleman, Michael '82, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 67, Folder 112)
    - Conley, William '83, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 67, Folder 113)
    - Daniel, Marc R. '83, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 67, Folder 114)
    - Vaswani, Prabha '83, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 67, Folder 115)
    - Martin, Stephanie '82, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 67, Folder 116)
    - Ellin, Phyllis M. '83, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 67, Folder 117)
    - Shivers, Julia '82, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 67, Folder 118)
    - Cooper, Leslie '82, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 67, Folder 119)
  - Freshman Summer Orientation Program (FSOP), Residential Advisors (RAA) and Minority Affairs Advisors (MAA), 1970-2000; 2 boxes; 1 folder
    - FSOP - Class of, 2000; 1996; 1 folder (Box 68, Folder 1)
    - MAA Program, 1986; 1 folder (Box 68, Folder 2)
    - RA/MAA Review, 1995-1996; 1 folder (Box 68, Folder 3)
    - MAA Review, 1994-1995; 1 folder (Box 68, Folder 4)
    - Spring Semester Schedule, 1996; 1 folder (Box 68, Folder 5)
    - 645-1010, 1995-1996; 1 folder (Box 68, Folder 6)
    - Mathey College, 1995; 1 folder (Box 68, Folder 7)
    - MAA Program Review, 1993; 1 folder (Box 68, Folder 8)
    - RA/MAA Application Information, 1993-1994; 1 folder (Box 68, Folder 9)
    - MAAs, 1991-1997; 1 box
      - Activities, 1993-1994; 1 folder (Box 68, Folder 10)
      - Evaluations, 1993-1994; 1 folder (Box 68, Folder 11)
      - Budget, 1993-1994; 1 folder (Box 68, Folder 12)
      - Program, 1993-1994; 1 folder (Box 68, Folder 13)
      - Program - Budget, Invoices, 1992-1993; 1 folder (Box 68, Folder 14)
      - Program, 1993; 1 folder (Box 68, Folder 15)
      - Applications, 1992-1993; 1 folder (Box 68, Folder 16)
      - 1995-1997, 2 folders (Box 68, Folder 17-18)
      - Hiring, 1995-1997; 3 folders (Box 68, Folder 19-21)
      - 1991-1992, 1 folder (Box 68, Folder 21)
      - 1992-1993, 1 folder (Box 68, Folder 22)
    - Account #645-1010, 1993-1994; 1 folder (Box 68, Folder 23)
    - Activities, 1994-1995; 1 folder (Box 68, Folder 24)
    - Hiring, 1994-1995; 1 folder (Box 68, Folder 25)
    - Program, 1994-1995; 1 folder (Box 68, Folder 26)
    - 645-1010, 1994; 1 folder (Box 68, Folder 27)
    - RA/MAA Advising Training, Spring, 1994; 1 folder (Box 68, Folder 28)
    - MAAs, 1997; 1 folder (Box 68, Folder 29)
    - Freshman Feedback on MAA's, 1995-1996; 1 folder (Box 68, Folder 30)
    - MAA Evaluations, 1995-1996; 1 folder (Box 68, Folder 31)
    - Evaluation and Outline, Spring '95/MAA Training, 1995-1996; 1 folder (Box 68, Folder 32)
    - RAs, 1970s; 1 folder (Box 68, Folder 33)
    - FSOP Master Files, 1997; 1 folder (Box 68, Folder 34)
    - FSOP, 1990; 1 box
      - Budget, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 68, Folder 35)
      - Course Choice, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 68, Folder 36)
      - Faculty Course, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 68, Folder 37)
      - Invitation Letter, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 68, Folder 38)
      - Letters to Staff, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 68, Folder 39)
      - Meetings, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 68, Folder 40)
      - Miscellaneous, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 68, Folder 41)
      - Peer Counselor Tutors (PCT), dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 68, Folder 42)
      - S Forms (Summer Program), dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 68, Folder 43)
    - FSOP 1996-1997 Evaluation, 1 folder (Box 69, Folder 1)
    - Evaluation for FSOP (Blank Forms), 1997; 1 folder (Box 69, Folder 2)
    - Extra Blank Evaluation Forms, undated; 1 folder (Box 69, Folder 3)
    - FSOP '92 Evaluation, 1992; 1 folder (Box 69, Folder 4)
    - FSOP Preliminary Evaluation, 1992 January; 1 folder (Box 69, Folder 5)
    - FSOP Payroll Info, 1993-1995; 1 folder (Box 69, Folder 6)
    - FSOP Dining Services, Summer, 1995; 1 folder (Box 69, Folder 7)
    - FSOP/MAA End of the Year Party, 1994 May; 1 folder (Box 69, Folder 8)
    - FSOP Expenses, 1993; 1 folder (Box 69, Folder 9)
    - 1992-1993, 1 folder (Box 69, Folder 10)
    - Page Catering, 1997; 1 folder (Box 69, Folder 11)
    - 645-1033, 1996-1997; 1 folder (Box 69, Folder 12)
    - FSOP '95 Expenses, 1996-1997; 1 folder (Box 69, Folder 13)
    - FSOP '95 Evaluations, 1995; 1 folder (Box 69, Folder 14)
    - FSOP Evaluation, 1995-1996; 1 folder (Box 69, Folder 15)
    - FSOP Course Evaluations, 1995; 1 folder (Box 69, Folder 16)
    - Program Evaluation FSOP, 1994; 1 folder (Box 69, Folder 17)
    - FSOP '92 Evaluation (Questionnaire), H. Spears, 1992; 1 folder (Box 69, Folder 18)
    - FSOP '92 Evaluations Instructors, 1992 August-September, 1 folder (Box 69, Folder 19)
    - FSOP '97 Course Evaluations, 1997; 1 folder (Box 69, Folder 20)
    - FSOP Follow-Up Letter, 1993; 1 folder (Box 69, Folder 21)
    - FSOP Group Leader Applications, 1994; 1 folder (Box 69, Folder 22)
    - FSOP Selection '98, 1994; 1 folder (Box 69, Folder 23)
    - FSOP Information, 1995; 1 folder (Box 69, Folder 24)
    - FSOP, 1995-1996; 1 folder (Box 69, Folder 25)
    - FSOP '95 Summer Program, 1995; 1 folder (Box 69, Folder 26)
    - FSOP '99 Expenses, 1995; 1 folder (Box 69, Folder 27)
    - FSOP '93 - General Information and Participation, 1993; 1 folder (Box 69, Folder 28)
    - FSOP, 1992-1993; 1 folder (Box 69, Folder 29)
    - FSOP '92 Faculty Folder, 1992; 1 folder (Box 69, Folder 30)
    - FSOP Information, Brochures, and Letters, 1994; 1 folder (Box 69, Folder 31)
    - Interim FSOP Working File, 1992; 1 folder (Box 69, Folder 32)
    - FSOP Lists, 1993; 1 folder (Box 69, Folder 33)
    - FSOP Invitees, 1993; 1 folder (Box 69, Folder 34)
    - FSOP Applications, 1993; 1 folder (Box 69, Folder 35)
    - FSOP Follow-Up, 1993; 1 folder (Box 69, Folder 36)
    - Class of 1999 FSOP Program, 1995, 1 folder (Box 69, Folder 37)
    - Untitled, 1992-1995; 2 folders (Box 69, Folder 38-39)
    - Group Leader Application, Spring, 1994; 1 folder (Box 69, Folder 40)
    - FSOP, Class of '97, 1993; 1 folder (Box 69, Folder 41)
    - 645-1033, 1995-1996; 1 folder (Box 69, Folder 42)
    - FSOP Miscellaneous, 1996; 1 folder (Box 69, Folder 43)
    - FSOP, 1996-1997; 1 folder (Box 69, Folder 44)
    - FSOP Summer Program, 1996; 1 folder (Box 69, Folder 45)
    - FSOP Sample Folder, 1993; 1 folder (Box 69, Folder 46)
    - FSOP Telephone Questionnaire, 1994; 1 folder (Box 69, Folder 47)
    - FSOP Participants and Invitees, 1994; 1 folder (Box 69, Folder 48)
    - FSOP - Eduardo Pagan Correspondence, 1992; 1 folder (Box 69, Folder 49)
    - FSOP Invitation Letter, Class of, 1997; 1993; 1 folder (Box 69, Folder 50)
    - FSOP Progress Report, 1994; 1 folder (Box 69, Folder 51)
    - FSOP Part I, Sample Memos to Speakers, Etc, 1994; 1 folder (Box 69, Folder 52)
    - FSOP Evaluations (Originals), undated; 1 folder (Box 69, Folder 53)
    - FSOP Evaluations (Duplicates), undated; 1 folder (Box 69, Folder 54)
  - "PULSE" and Upperclass Life, 1984-1988; 1 folder (Box 70, Folder 1)
  - Recruitment Issues (Equal Opportunity Policy), 1984-1989; 1 folder (Box 70, Folder 2)
  - Robert Spencer, 1987-1988; 1 folder (Box 70, Folder 3)
  - FSOP/EOP, 1988-1990; 1 folder (Box 70, Folder 4)
  - FSOP/EOP Program, 1982-1987; 1 folder (Box 70, Folder 5)
  - FSOP/Pew, 1987-1992; 1 folder (Box 70, Folder 6)
  - Letters in Support of College Associate Program, 1986; 1 folder (Box 70, Folder 7)
  - College Associate Program - Application Materials, 1986-1987; 1 folder (Box 70, Folder 8)
  - Residential College Associate Program, 1987-1988; 1 folder (Box 70, Folder 9)
  - Residential College Associate Program - AY, 1987-1988; 1 folder (Box 70, Folder 10)
  - College Associates, 1988-1989; 1 folder (Box 70, Folder 11)
  - College Associates, 1989-1990; 1 folder (Box 70, Folder 12)
  - Minority Affairs Advisors, 1992-1993; 1 folder (Box 70, Folder 13)
  - Residential Advisors, 1984-1992; 1 box
    - 1984-1985, 1 folder (Box 70, Folder 14)
    - 1985-1986, 1 folder (Box 70, Folder 15)
    - 1986-1987, 1 folder (Box 70, Folder 16)
    - 1987-1988, 1 folder (Box 70, Folder 17)
    - 1988-1989, 1 folder (Box 70, Folder 18)
    - 1989-1990, 1 folder (Box 70, Folder 19)
    - 1990-1991, 1 folder (Box 70, Folder 20)
    - 1991-1992, 1 folder (Box 70, Folder 21)
  - Resident & Minority Affairs Advisor Manuals, 1984-1993; 1 folder (Box 70, Folder 22)
  - RA/MAA Review Materials, 1995; 1 folder (Box 70, Folder 23)
  - Stevenson Hall, 1971-1984; 1 folder (Box 70, Folder 24)
  - Yavneh House, 1971; 1 folder (Box 70, Folder 25)
  - Princeton Inn College, 1973-1981; 1 folder (Box 70, Folder 26)
  - Wilson College, 1970-1979; 1 folder (Box 70, Folder 27)
  - College Miscellany, 1970-1981; 1 folder (Box 70, Folder 28)
  - Madison Society/New South, 1974-1978; 1 folder (Box 70, Folder 29)
  - Masters' Guidelines, 1970-1981; 1 folder (Box 70, Folder 30)
  - Series 4: Residential Advisors, undated; 1 item
- Series 5: Audiovisual, 1976 October-1988; 2 boxes
  The Audiovisual series consists of two boxes of VHS tapes containing video documentation of various student and campus activities. Ascertaining the exact date of many of the events in the videos is difficult, however the tapes generally encompass the years 1985-1986.
  The arrangement of the materials at the time of transfer has been retained.
  - Video Cassettes, 1985-1988; 2 boxes
    - Bonfire and Yale Game, 1986 February 28; 1 box (Box 71)
    - Packet Sports, Class Day, 1986; 1 box (Box 71)
    - Video Year Book Tape 3, 1985 November 18-19; 1 box (Box 71)
    - Candlelight Concert, 1985 December 14; 1 box (Box 71)
    - Triangle, 1985; 1 box
      - Close 1/1, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 71)
      - Wide 1/2, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 71)
      - Edited, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 71)
    - PTU Preview, 1986 March 3; 1 box (Box 71)
    - Woodrow Wilson School Faculty Feud, 1986 March 7; 1 box (Box 71)
    - Mime Show - Theatre Intime, 1986 September 20 (Original), 1 box (Box 71)
    - Yale Whiffenpoofs, 1985 November 16; 1 box (Box 71)
    - Expressions, Fall, 1985; 1 box (Box 71)
    - Christmas Arch, 1985 December 9; 1 box (Box 71)
    - Graduation - Commencement, 1985; 1 box (Box 71)
    - Guatemala Speech, 1985 March 8-May 8; 1 box
      - Speech on Guatemala, 1985 May 8; 1 box (Box 71)
      - Guatemala Speech 1/1, 1985 March 8; 1 box (Box 71)
    - "Funstigators!" Final Edit, 1985; 1 box (Box 71)
    - Video Year Book, 1985; 1 box
      - Video Year Book Tape 5, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 71)
      - Video Year Book Tape 12, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 71)
      - Dub of Video Year Book Sections, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 71)
      - Video Year Book Sections, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 71)
    - Aerobic Shoot, undated; 1 box (Box 71)
    - Jadwin Weights, undated; 1 box (Box 71)
    - Yoga Shoot, undated; 1 box (Box 71)
    - Mime's The Word (Final Edit), undated; 1 box (Box 71)
    - Nassau Hall - Bowen, Commencement, undated; 1 box (Box 71)
    - GFV Archive Tape, undated; 1 box (Box 71)
    - Dillon Weight Training, undated; 1 box (Box 71)
    - Jadwin Agility Training, undated; 1 box (Box 71)
    - International Center, 1985 October-December; 1 box
      - International Center (Festival), Outtakes, undated; 1 box (Box 71)
      - International Center Tape 1, 1985 October; 1 box (Box 71)
      - International Center Tape 2, 1985 November-December; 1 box (Box 71)
    - Virginia Woolf, dates not examined; 1 box
      - Virginia Woolf, Tape 2, undated; 1 box (Box 71)
      - Virginia Woolf - Ground Floor Video, Part 1 and 2, undated; 1 box (Box 71)
    - Ground Floor Video, undated; 1 box (Box 71)
    - Melissa/Jogging, undated; 1 box (Box 71)
    - Princeton Professor's Favorite Recipes Show Segment 1, undated; 1 box (Box 71)
    - Princeton #1, Burn Code, undated; 1 box (Box 71)
    - (Edited Master), undated; 1 box (Box 71)
    - Princeton #3-6, Burn Code, undated; 1 box (Box 71)
    - Burn Code #4, undated; 1 box (Box 71)
    - Unlabelled, undated; 1 box (Box 71)
    - Video Yearbook - Prom, 1986; 1 box (Box 72)
    - Princeton Yearbook, 1986; 1 box (Box 72)
    - Video Yearbook Tape 11 - Lawn Parties, 1986; 1 box (Box 72)
    - Communiversity, 1986; 1 box (Box 72)
    - Princeton Video Yearbook, 1986; 1 box (Box 72)
    - Forbes #1-2, 1985 May; 1 box (Box 72)
    - International Center Tape 3, 1985 December; 1 box (Box 72)
    - Video Year Book (Promo), 1988; 1 box (Box 72)
    - Coeducation #2 - Super Bowl, undated; 1 box (Box 72)
    - "Today Show", undated; 1 box (Box 72)
    - Unlabelled, undated; 1 box (Box 72)
  - Student Life Discussion - Trustees Meeting, 1976 October 21, 1 box (Box 72)
- Series 6: Student Discipline, 1905-2015; 62 boxes
  The Student Discipline series contains records relating to the Dean of Students' oversight of student discipline. The bulk of the records consist of files on individual students documenting specific disciplinary infractions and their corresponding penalties.
  Mainly arranged chronologically by year and alphabetically thereunder.
  Student Discipline files are closed during the lifetime of the student. To safeguard privacy, no folder list has been included in this finding aid.